Nguyen Xuan Quang

💌 xquang.n@gmail.com | in xuanquang | 🗘 xuanquang | 🤳 0935 386 039

Summary

I recently passed the AWS Solution Architect Associate Certification after completing the AWS Restart course. My ability to learn new things passionately, provide clear instructions, and advise users on new system features are among my strongest skills. The company recognized me for effectively assisting a coworker at work.

AWS Cloud Projects

Certifications

Doing labs helped me learn a service and gain real life experience with AWS.

https://xuanquang.github.io/posts/aws-labs/







Education

AWS re/Start Vietnam

May 2022 - Present

- Learning the fundamentals of AWS Cloud. Using scenario-based exercises, practical labs, and coursework to help students learn more.
- Hands-on experience with EC2, ELB, S3, VPC, VPC peering, Subnet, Route table, VPC Endpoint, Security group, Network ACL, IAM, RDS, Aurora, DynamoDB, Lambda, Autoscaling, etc.
- · I'm studying my way through cloudjourney.awsstudygroup.com and cloudacademy.com labs.

Thinking School

April 2020 – Present

• Students can take online classes and communicate with instructors in real time because of Thinking School's system. I hold the following certificates: Using an LMS to manage training and learning, Make and edit a movie, etc.

Quy Nhon University

Sept 2005 – June 2009

· Bachelor of Accountancy

Experience

ISPACE VOCATIONAL TRAINING COLLEGE

2020 - 2022

Secretary

- * Organized, coordinated, and took notes during meetings.
- * Handled administrative tasks and supported the sales team.
- * Created content about Online Safety on the website.

FAMILY'S GROCERY STORE

2016 - 2019

- * Managed my family's grocery store.
- * Helped customers feel happy when they met me at the grocery store.

SILICON STRAITS SAIGON

2013 - 2015

Customer Success Specialist

- * Participated in and managed a wide range of CognitoCRM-related tasks, including proposal presentations, client meetings, product releases, and new feature training.
- * Listened to the customer's needs and recommended a solution.
- * Wrote FAQs, guidelines, and tutorials to support sales staff members' understanding of interesting product features and enabled them to close more deals.
- * Participated in the Quality Assurance process to ensure that customers received a high-quality product.

TGM CORPORATION 2010 – 2013

Online Customer Support

- * Created email marketing campaigns to promote products or services.
- * Executed newsletter projects that shared useful information to customers.
- * Managed company's Facebook fanpages and websites.
- * Developed online communities: Vuon Toi Thanh Cong forum (about 30.000 members)

Volunteer

LEAD LIKE JESUS VIETNAM

2021 - Present

lanhdaonhugiesu.com

· Manage and grow the marketing channels.

MUC DONG MAGAZINE

2017 - Present

tapsanmucdong.net

· Make suggestions for improving the paper products.

VIETNAM CATHOLIC LITERATURE

2017 - 2020

vanthoconggiao.net

· Collected articles and posted on the website.

Preferences

Mr Bui Hai An

Deputy CEO at Timo Vietnam **Phone number**: 0949 646 899

Mr Do Tran Binh Minh

Excutive Vice President of iSPACE - Cyber Security College

Phone number: 0973 483 961